[Music]
s shaming now if you're unfamiliar with
the term uh it's what people use uh or
it's when people use women's own
sexuality As Weapons against them it's
like the stop hitting yourself thing
your big brother used to do you
know but with vaginas instead of
hands thank you for not illustrating a
vagina hand like I'm never going to be
like I'm a dick but if my friend is like
wearing flanel chopping wood I'll be
like hey dke what's up you
knowon why would you have sex with your
friend um okay so you're pretty Advanced
because because like you you haven't had
sex in a while or you're just like you
see them in a different light they turn
around you're like oh my God it's you
and then you do sex with them do you
know sex what does the benefit the
benefit of sex a friend sex oh the
benefit is the sex is the orgasms
hopefully no orgasms goes back to friend
how do
you hey America Larry Wilmore here if
you like the nightly show on Comedy
Central like us on Facebook too just
don't poke me I do not like being poked
you can Candy Crush me